<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Vanilla Christmas Expanded</name>
  <packageId>VE.VanillaChristmasExpanded</packageId>
  <author>Oskar Potocki, Sarg Bjornson, Taranchuk</author>
 <modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/VELogo</modIconPath>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
  <supportedVersions>
   
    <li>1.5</li><li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
 <loadAfter>
		
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>
  <description>Festive season is approaching us fast, and I think it’s proper that Vanilla Expanded releases a big mod to celebrate that time. It’s been a very productive year for us, and with some festive content, we get to breathe, enjoy and celebrate this beautiful time of the year.

Vanilla Christmas Expanded is a resurrection of one of our first mods which also shared this title. The goal of the mod is very straight forward: bring festivities to your RimWorld colony. We won’t focus on celebrations of any particular culture or country, and instead plan to bring a lot of unique festive flavor from all around the world.

This mod operates in a form of an Advent calendar. This means that every day, something new will be added, and the description of the mod will be updated with a new infographic, showcasing what was added. This means that if you’re interested, you can come back to the mod description every day to see what new content will appear in your game!

The content will vary - on some days, it will be a small trinket or a decoration, on others, it will be a brand new mechanic or system. Overall, however, this should be a pretty beefy Christmas mod that brings the joy to your game, rewarding you for celebrating it with presents, high spirits and good events.

Credit: Snow sound by max_b_jo -- https://freesound.org/s/269851/ -- License: Attribution 4.0
</description>
 
</ModMetaData>